https://www.hertzfurniture.com/privacy.html

COVID-19 Guidance
We appreciate the trust you place in Hertz Furniture and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from this website.
We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please contact our Customer Service department at 800-526-4677.
Personal Information We Collect
We may collect information (including name, address, telephone number, email address and, when necessary, credit card information) when you:
Place an order from our catalogs or on our website
Return an item or make an exchange
Inquire about our services
Request a catalog
Request color swatches
Request a scheduled call
Enter a contest or sweepstakes
Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
Participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event
We refer to this information as “Order Information.” We maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database unless and until you ask us to delete this information. To serve you best, we may combine this information with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources whose policies meet the Direct Marketing Association’s privacy standards.
We also automatically gather information about your device as you navigate through our website via cookies, session tags, log files, and JavaScript. This information about your device may include information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
Using Information We Collect
At Hertz Furniture, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and fulfill your orders exactly as you have requested. As a result, your information may be used for the following purposes:
Process and track your order
Provide the services you request
Contact you about the status of an order
Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
Customize our communications to you
Provide information concerning product recalls or products you have purchased
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud
Improve our merchandise selection and customer service
Improve and optimize our website by studying how our customers browse and interact with the site, which products they search for
Assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns
Recognize you when you return to our website
If you set your browser to refuse cookies, please call us at 800-526-4677 to place your order.
Information We Share with Others and Your Privacy Rights
We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including credit card processing, shipping, email distribution, market research, and promotions management. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Hertz Furniture.
We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:
https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.
You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.
Your Choices
We offer choices about the types of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive catalogs or other communications from Hertz Furniture or if you prefer to receive them less frequently, please contact us at the address shown below.
Please be sure to provide us your exact name and address, or the mailing label from your catalog, so that we can be sure to identify you correctly. Because mailings are planned in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If, due to human error, you continue to receive unwanted communications, please contact us again and we will make every effort to correct the situation.
We may use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.
For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:
http://optout.aboutads.info/.
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.
Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to the United States.
How We Use Email
When you provide us with your email address, we may send you emails necessary to process your order or respond to a request.
It is our intent to send you promotional email only if you have agreed to receive it.
Updating or Reviewing your Information
To update your customer information (name, address, telephone number, or email address), please contact us at info@hertzfurniture.com. To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before you update or review your information.
Security
It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you. We use a variety of current technologies and processes for protection of our customer data. We limit the information we provide to outside companies with whom we contract to only what they need to carry out their responsibilities.
When you make a purchase, request a catalog, or create an account on our website, your transactional information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format using VeriSign SSL technology.
Privacy of Children on our website
Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
Policy Changes
From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will post these changes on our website. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.
What is the Verification Code?
Alternatively called CVV2 (Visa), CVC2 (MasterCard), or CID (American Express), the verification code is a three- or four-digit number that appears on your card after the account number.
For Visa, MasterCard, and Discover cards, the number is located on the back of your card near your signature. The number on these cards is three digits long.
For American Express cards, the number is located on the front of your card, on the right hand side above your card number. The number on American Express cards is four digits long.
This number serves as an added layer of security, because it ensures that the card is physically in possession of the user at the time of purchase. Merchants such as Hertz Furniture will request the code at checkout from the cardholder, and the information is sent electronically to the card-issuing bank to verify its validity. For added protection, merchants are prohibited from keeping or storing these numbers after the transaction has been completed.
Questions or Comments?
For questions, comments, or assistance, we invite you to contact us by phone at
or by email at info@hertzfurniture.com. We hope to answer any questions to your satisfaction, but should you ever want to contact a third party regarding our privacy practices, you can email the Direct Marketing Association’s Committee on Ethical Business Practices at privacypromise@the-dma.org. The DMA is the oldest and largest association for consumers and companies with interest in direct marketing.
